Finding Aid for School of Nursing (University of Michigan) records, 1891-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean Rhoda Russell, 1891-1972
  - Topical File, 1891-1972
    - Burton, Marion, 1921-1923 (Box 8)
    - Chemistry, 1954-1957 (Box 8)
    - Choir, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Christian Medical Society, 1950-1961 (Box 8)
    - Class Credits and Honor Points, 1929-1931 (Box 8)
    - Class Lists, 1936-1954; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Classroom Needs, 1955-1961 (Box 8)
    - Clinical Instruction Material, 1946-1947 (Box 8)
    - Clinical Practice Time, 1954-1964 (Box 8)
    - Commencement Lists, 1944-1967 (Box 8)
    - Community Inquiries, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Conferences and Workshops
      - 1957 (Box 9)
      - 1958 (Box 9)
      - 1959 (Box 9)
      - 1960 (Box 9)
      - 1961 (Box 9)
      - 1967 (Box 9)
      - 1968
        - Workshop I (Box 9)
        - Workshop II (Box 9)
      - 1969
        - Coronary Care (Box 9)
        - Inservice (Box 9)
      - 1970
        - Cancer (Box 9)
        - Cardiovascular (Box 9)
        - Coronary Care (Box 9)
        - Inservice, 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Stroke (Box 9)
        - Terminally Ill (Box 9)
      - 1971
        - Coronary care (Box 9)
        - Inservice (Box 9)
        - Terminally Ill (Box 9)
    - Consultation (Minnesota), 1950 (Box 9)
    - Convocation Honors, 1939-1950 (Box 9)
    - Curriculum
      - Evaluation of Undergraduate Program, 1972 (Box 9)
      - Four Year Degree Program
        - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 9)
        - Survey of Graduates, 1956-1960 (Box 9)
      - Four Year Proposal, 1968/69 (Box 9)
      - Integration of Psychiatric Nursing and Mental Health Concepts into Curriculum, 1962 (Box 9)
      - Pass-Fail, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
      - Revisal, 1950-1954; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Dean (Box 10)
      - Of Graduate School, 1953; 1965 (Box 10)
      - Of Women, 1947-1961 (Box 10)
    - Dedication of Medical Center, 1959 (Box 10)
    - Delta College, 1961-1962; 1969 (Box 10)
    - Diehl, Elisa, 1967-1970 (Box 10)
    - Enrollment, 1954-1972 (Box 10)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Report, 1963-1969 (Box 10)
    - Farrell, Marie (Dean, Boston University School of Nursing), 1957 (Box 10)
    - Federal Aid, 1942 (Box 10)
    - Fisk, Beatrice, 1959-1961 (Box 10)
    - Flint Campus (University of Michigan), 1955-1956 (Box 10)
    - Foreign Students, 1955 (Box 10)
    - Fralick, Bruce (Nurses Training Proposal), 1961 (Box 10)
    - Fresh Air Camp, 1957-1962 (Box 10)
    - Freshman Class Analysis (Pharmacy), 1971-1972 (Box 10)
    - Freshman Counseling, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - Future Planning, 1944; 1958-1963 (Box 10)
    - Gerontology, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
    - Graduate Program
      - General, 1963 (Box 10)
      - Loan and Scholarship Aid, 1963 (Box 10)
      - Maternal-Child Health, 1962-1969 (Box 10)
      - Medical-Surgical Nursing
        - Original Proposal, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
        - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
        - Progress Reports
          - 1962 (Box 10)
          - 1963-1964 (Box 10)
          - 1965-1968 (Box 10)
        - Psychiatric Nursing
          - Original Proposal, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
          - Material for Report, 1961-1962 (Box 10)
          - Organizational Chart, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Haynes, Harley, 1928-1943 (Box 10)
    - Health Sciences, Division of
      - 1941-1947 (Box 10)
      - 1972 (Box 10)
    - History
      - General History, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - University Hospital History (Box 11)
    - Hospital and Medical Economics Study, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Housing, 1909; circa 1942 (Box 11)
    - Hutchins, H.B., 1919 (Box 11)
    - Industrial Nursing, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Kellogg Foundation
      - 1947-1949 (Box 11)
      - 1956-1959 (Box 11)
    - Kerlikowske, A.C., 1944-1949 (Box 11)
    - Lambertson, Eleanor, 1961-1962 (Box 11)
    - Lewis (Rev.) Memorial Fund, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Library Expansion, 1960-1961 (Box 11)
    - Little, Clarence Cook, 1926 (Box 11)
    - Lutheran Hospital Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - Maternity Education, 1955-1956 (Box 11)
    - Mattone, Edythe, 1963 (Box 11)
    - McCain, R. Faye, 1964 (Box 11)
    - McNeil, Ella, 1949-1959 (Box 11)
      (see also "Awards" Box 32)
    - Medical Center Journal
      - 1965/66 (Box 11)
      - 1966/67 (Box 11)
    - Medical Office Assistants, 1960-1961 (Box 11)
    - Medical Science Building, 1953-1957; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Medical Staff (Senior), 1968-1969 (Box 11)
    - Mental Retardation Facility, 1965; 1967 (Box 11)
    - Mercer, Lianne S. and Phyllis Cantwell Nicolaou, Attitude Change of Student Nurses Toward Traits of the Ideal Nurse, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Michigan Association for Regional Medical Programs
      - Advisory Committee for Continuing Education, 1968-1970 (Box 11)
      - Basic Coronary Care Nursing Courses, 1969-1970 (Box 11)
      - Basic Coronary Care Subcommittees, 1969 (Box 11)
      - Cancer Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Diagram of Activities (Box 11)
      - Grant Proposal
        - Initial and Miscellaneous, 1966-1973 (Box 11)
        - Five Year Proposal, 1968 (Box 11)
        - Second Operational Year Proposal, 1969 (Box 11)
      - Heart, Cancer and Stroke, 1969-1972 (Box 12)
      - Heustis, Albert E., Director, 1968-1971 (Box 12)
      - Professional Advisory Council for Stroke, 1969 (Box 12)
      - Regional Planning, 1968 (Box 12)
      - Regional Stroke Program (Proposed), 1969 (Box 12)
      - Reports
        - 1964-1967 (Box 12)
        - (Annual), 1967 (Box 12)
        - (Annual), 1968 (Box 12)
        - (Quarterly), 1969 (Box 12)
        - (Annual), 1970 (Box 12)
        - (Miscellaneous), 1968-1971 (Box 12)
      - Russell, Rhoda Reddig, Undated (Box 12)
      - Target Dates, 1967-1970 (Box 12)
      - Task Force on Continuing Education, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Michigan Citizens Commission on Higher Education, 1964-1965 (Box 12)
    - Michigan Comprehensive Coronary Care Project
      - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Annual Report, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents
      - Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 12)
      - Pilot Cost Study, 1970-1971 (Box 12)
      - Report Re: Nursing, 1955; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Michigan League of Nursing
      - Board of Directors
        - 1960 (Box 13)
        - 1961 (Box 13)
        - 1962 (Box 13)
        - 1963 (Box 13)
      - Collegiate Nursing Education, Committee on, 1953-1956 (Box 13)
      - Committee Assignment Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
      - Membership Dues, 1956-1959 (Box 13)
      - Permanent Conference Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
      - South Central League, 1955-1962 (Box 13)
      - State Board of Alcoholism, 1958-1960 (Box 13)
      - Steering Committee, 1953-1956 (Box 13)
      - Study of Hospital and Medical Economics, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
    - Michigan State Federation of Women's Clubs, 1948-1949 (Box 13)
    - Michigan State Government
      - Board of Nursing
        - Correspondence, 1914; 1951-1953 (Box 13)
        - List of Classes, 1942-1960 (Box 13)
        - Operating Room Proposal, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
        - Reports (Generally Annual)
          - 1928-1944 (Box 13)
          - 1944-1956 (Box 13)
          - 1958-1961 (Box 13)
          - 1963-1972 (Box 13)
          - Special, 1969 (Box 13)
          - Visits, Reports of, 1941-1961 (Box 14)
        - Traverse City Community Survey, 1957 (Box 14)
      - Department of Health
        - Corneliuson, Goldie B., 1956-1960 (Box 14)
        - Guide to Patients with Communicable Diseases, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
        - Maternity Project
          - Advisory Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 14)
          - Contracts and Reports, 1953-1957 (Box 14)
          - General, 1947-1958 (Box 14)
        - Retarded Children, 1957 (Box 14)
      - Department of Public Instruction, 1965-1971 (Box 14)
    - Michigan State Nurses Association
      - Committees
        - Economic Security, Committee on, 1960-1962; 1963; 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Hospital and Medical Economics Study Committee
          - Hearing Materials, 1960-1962 (Box 14)
          - Comments, 1959 (Box 14)
          - Minutes and Membership Lists, 1961 (Box 14)
        - Program Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1955-1961 (Box 14)
      - Counseling and Placement, 1954-1961 (Box 14)
      - General, 1946 (Box 14)
    - National League of Nursing (NLN)
      - Accreditation
        - 1939 (Box 14)
        - 1948-1952 (Box 14)
        - 1953
          - Report (Box 14)
        - 1956
          - Report (Box 14)
          - Correspondence Re: Site Visit (Box 14)
          - Report of Site Visitors (Box 14)
        - 1957
          - Correspondence (Includes 1958) (Box 14)
          - Report for NLN, February, 2 folders (Box 15)
          - Supplementary Report of Visitors (Box 15)
          - Report of Visitors (includes 1958) (Box 15)
        - 1958 (Box 15)
        - 1959
          - Progress Report, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - 1963
          - Report for Accreditation and Supplementary Reports, 5 folders (Box 15)
          - Correspondence re: Site Visit (Box 15)
          - Report of Site Visit (Correspondence to 1964) (Box 15)
          - Accreditation Report (Box 15)
        - 1965 (Box 16)
          - Progress Report (Box 16)
        - 1968 (Box 16)
        - 1969
          - Supplementary Reports for Accreditation, 3 folders (Box 16)
          - Report of Site Visitors (Box 16)
          - Accreditation Report (Box 16)
        - 1970
          - Correspondence, 1948-1961 (Box 16)
      - Consultation Visit, 1963 (Box 16)
      - Cost Studies, 1952-1960 (Box 16)
      - Enrollment in Collegiate Program, 1954-1955 (Box 16)
      - Medical-Surgical Nursing, 1959 (Box 16)
      - Meetings
        - 1956
          - Chicago (January) (Box 16)
          - Chicago (November) (Box 16)
        - 1958
          - Chicago (February) (Box 16)
          - Chicago (March) (Box 16)
        - 1959
          - Philadelphia (Box 16)
        - 1960
          - Chicago (February) (Box 16)
          - St. Louis (Fall) (Box 16)
        - 1961
          - Kansas City (November) (Box 16)
        - 1962
          - Phoenix (November) (Box 16)
        - 1963
          - Atlantic City (May) (Box 16)
        - 1967
          - New York (May) (Box 16)
          - Las Vegas (November) (Box 16)
        - 1968
          - Cleveland (February) (Box 16)
          - Milwaukee (March) (Box 16)
      - Public Health
        - Conferences, 1951; 1956 (Box 16)
        - General (Box 17)
          - 1958-1959 (Box 17)
          - 1960 (Box 17)
        - Tuttle, Mildred L., Undated (Box 17)
      - Public Law for Nursing Education Facilities, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
      - Reports
        - 1943-1960 (Box 17)
        - 1961-1967 (Box 17)
      - Shetland, Margaret L., 1959-1960 (Box 17)
      - Statement of Nursing Education, 1954 (Box 17)
      - Statistics on Nursing Education, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Neuropsychiatric Institute, 1955 (Box 17)
    - New York State Nursing Reports
      - 1917-1940 (Box 17)
      - 1941-1954 (Box 17)
    - Niehuss, Marvin L., Undated (Box 17)
    - Notes on Hospital Training School, 1913 (Box 17)
    - Nurse Orientation Schedules, Undated (Box 17)
    - Nurses Employment, Study of, 1957 (Box 17)
    - Nursing 40 Course, 1958 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Activities Study Report
      - 1948 (Box 17)
      - 1948-1952 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Assessment, 1965-1967 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Council (Medical Center), 1971 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Current Account Study, 1957 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Needs and Resources in Michigan, Report, 1966 (Box 17)
    - Nursing Needs and Resources, Southeastern Michigan Forecast, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Nutrition Correspondence, 1955 (Box 17)
    - Obstetrics and Pediatrics Infections, 1957 (Box 17)
    - Obstetrical Nursing, 1953-1958 (Box 17)
    - Obstetrics Institute, 1955-1956 (Box 17)
    - Obstetrics Nursing Referral Project, 1950-1954 (Box 17)
    - Operating Room Questionnaire, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Organization, School of Nursing, 1941 (Box 17)
    - Patient Roll Report, circa 1949 (Box 18)
    - Pediatric Surgery, Medical Service Plan Implementation, 1974 (Box 18)
    - Pharmacy, medicine, Nursing Planning Conference, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Phelps, Terry
      - Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 18)
      - Course and Conference Material, 1958-1960 (Box 18)
    - Physical Therapy, 1952-1958 (Box 18)
    - Prepaid Hospital and Medical Care Plans, Statement about Michigan State Nurses Association and Michigan League of Nurses, 1962 (Box 18)
    - Progress Report, School of Nursing, 1945 (Box 18)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Plan, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Public Health Nursing
      - Affiliations, 1957-1960 (Box 18)
      - Contract Material, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
      - Correspondence
        - 1949-1953 (Box 18)
        - 1954 (Box 18)
        - 1955-1961 (Box 18)
        - (Josephine Brown), 1961-1963 (Box 18)
      - Detroit Health Department, 1965-1972 (Box 18)
      - Faculty, 1964 (Box 18)
      - General, 1962-1963 (Box 18)
      - Gibson, William C., 1954-1960 (Box 18)
      - Meeting, April 11, 1963 (Box 18)
      - Memos, Conferences, etc., 1949-1954 (Box 18)
      - Nursing Study, 1972 (Box 18)
      - Planning
        - Curriculum, 1960-1963 (Box 18)
        - Nursing Experience, 1952-1959 (Box 18)
      - Survey Course, 1952 (Box 18)
      - Washtenaw County Health Department, 1963-1972 (Box 18)
      - Wayne State University Workshops, 1950-1954 (Box 18)
    - Ravitz, Mel Jerome (Dissertation Project), 1952-1953 (Box 19)
    - Referral Process Project, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
    - Rehabilitation Project (Proposed), 1955-1957 (Box 19)
    - RHP-Replacement Hospital Project, 1967 (Box 19)
    - Reports, School of Nursing
      - Annual
        - [incomplete], 1894-1936 (Box 19)
        - (President's), 1942-1947 (Box 19)
        - (President's) [incomplete], 1948-1967 (Box 19)
      - Monthly
        - 1916-1922 (Box 19)
        - 1922-1928, 1946-1947 (Box 19)
    - Requests for Information, 1959-1962 (Box 19)
    - Research by Clinical Nursing Specialists, 1965-1969 (Box 19)
    - RN Program, 1971 (Box 19)
    - Rules and Plans, circa 1930-1931 (Box 19)
    - Russell, Rhoda Reddig
      - 1942-1955 (Box 19)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    - Russell Sage Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
    - Ruthven, Alexander, 1943 (Box 19)
    - Sana, Josephine (Course Outlines), circa 1960s (Box 19)
    - Schering Corporation, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
    - Sigma Theta Tau
      - 1958-1971 (Box 19)
      - 1967-1972 (Box 19)
    - Simons Co. v. Hill-Rom Co. (Deposition of Rhoda Reddig Russell) (Box 19)
    - Smith, Allan, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - Social Director's Reports, 1936-1955 (Box 19)
    - Social Service Department, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
    - Social Work Course, 1958-1960 (Box 19)
    - Sociology Course, 1953 (Box 19)
    - Special Academic Projects, Office of, Annual Report, 1971 (Box 20)
    - Statistics, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Stirton, William, 1956-1959 (Box 20)
    - Students
      - Financial Needs, 1954-1962 (Box 20)
      - Government, 1926-1929; 1959 (Box 20)
      - Handbooks
        - 1949-1962 (Box 20)
        - 1963-1969 (Box 20)
      - Records
        - Attendance Books
          - 1899-1903 (Box 20)
          - 1904-1912 (Box 20)
          - 1907-1913 (Box 20)
        - Register of Freshmen, 1921-1944 (Box 20)
    - Summit Medical Center, Ann Arbor, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Team Nursing, 1955-1956 (Box 20)
    - Television, University of Michigan, 1955-1956 (Box 20)
    - Titus, Shirley C., Scholarship Fund, 1930; 1957 (Box 20)
    - Tuberculosis Advisory Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 20)
    - Tuberculosis Sanitarium, Jackson, 1957 (Box 20)
    - Two Year Programs
      - General, 1959 (Box 20)
      - Traverse City, 1957-1960 (Box 20)
    - Uniforms (for Students), 1954-1956 (Box 20)
      (includes fabric samples)
    - Unions, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
    - United States Public Health Service
      - Demonstration Project, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
      - General, 1960 (Box 20)
      - Integration Project, 1955-1957 (Box 20)
      - Neurological and Sensory Disease Traineeship Program, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
      - Research Grants Program, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
      - Traineeship Program, 1961-1962 (Box 20)
    - University Health Service Policies, 1945-1954 (Box 20)
    - University Hospital Medical Staff Manual, 1966 (Box 20)
    - Vaughan, Henry, Dean of School of Public Health, 1954-1955 (Box 21)
    - Visits to Ohio State University and University of Iowa, 1958 (Box 21)
    - Wayne State University, 1959-1961 (Box 21)
    - Williams, Robert
      - 1945-1956 (Box 21)
      - 1957-1962 (Box 21)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 21)
    - Woman's City Club, 1959-1961 (Box 21)
    - Women on Faculty, 1948-1953 (Box 21)
    - World War II, Nursing Units and Red Cross, 1939-1942 (Box 21)
    - Ypsilanti Hospital, Psychiatry, 1966-1969 (Box 21)
    - Zonta International, 1951-1960 (Box 21)
- Dean Carolyne K. Davis and Successors, 1968-1980
  The records of Dean Carolyne K. Davis and Successors (1968-1980) form the second subgroup in the School of Nursing papers. Included here are the papers of Dean Davis, Acting Dean Maxine Loomis, Dean Mary Lohr, and some of the papers of Acting Dean Norma E. Marshall. Portions of Dean Marshall's papers are also found in Dean Russell's material. The Davis and Successors subgroup have been arranged in the same way as the Russell subgroup. They have been divided into Committee and Faculty Records (1970-1980) and a Topical File (1968-1980).
  - Committee and Faculty Records, 1970-1980
    The Committee and Faculty Records have been subdivided into two subseries, Committee Records (1970-1980) and Faculty Records (1972-1974). Committee records have been arranged alphabetically and are most notable for the minutes of the Executive and Augmented Executive Committees (1972-1979 and 1974-1979 respectively). The Augmented Executive Committee is responsible for tenure and promotion decisions within the school. Faculty Records are very limited. Faculty meeting minutes are available only for the years 1972-1974.
    - Committee Records, 1970-1980
      - Advisory Council
        - 1972/73 (Box 21)
        - 1973/74 (Box 21)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1971/72 (Box 21)
        - 1972/73 (Box 21)
        - 1973/74 (Box 21)
      - Board of Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 21)
      - Committee on Committees, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
      - Community Health Chairperson Search, 1976-1977 (Box 21)
      - Continuing Education Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1972-1975; 3 folders (Box 21)
      - Curriculum Committee (Undergraduate)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 21)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 21)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 21)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 21)
      - Elections Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 21)
      - Executive Committee (Box 22)
        [See also Box 31]
        - 1972 (Box 22)
        - 1973, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - 1974 (Box 22)
        - 1975 (Box 22)
        - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 22)
      - Executive Committee (Augmented)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 22)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 22)
        - 1976-1977 (Box 22)
        - 1977-1978, 6 folders (Box 35)
        - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 35)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 23)
      - Formal Structure of the School of Nursing, Study Committee on, Report, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
      - Fundamentals Chairperson Search, 1977-1978 (Box 23)
      - Graduate Study Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
      - Health Industry Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 23)
      - Medical Center Committees
        - Administrative Staff
          - 1972 (Box 23)
          - 1973, 2 folders (Box 23)
        - Alumni Society
          - Board of Governors
            - Constitution and Bylaws, 1972 (Box 23)
            - Meeting Minutes, 1972-1973; 1979-1980; 5 folders (Box 23)
          - Alumni Visiting Committee, 1980 (Box 23)
        - Mini-Staff (Box 24)
          - 1973 (Box 24)
          - 1974 (Box 24)
        - Planning, 1972/73 (Box 24)
      - Orientation Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Psychiatric Chairperson Search
        - 1977/78 (Box 24)
        - 1978/79 (Box 24)
        - 1979/80 (Box 35)
      - Retardation Policy Committee
        - 1970-1972 (Box 24)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 24)
      - Saint Joseph Hospital Task Force, 1972 (Box 24)
      - Scholastic Standing Committee
        - 1972/73 (Box 24)
        - 1973/74 (Box 24)
        - 1974/75 (Box 24)
      - Space-Building Committee
        - 1975-1977 (Box 24)
        - 1977/78, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - Veterans Administration, 1973/74 (Box 24)
    - Faculty Records, 1972-1974
      - Conference, 1973 (Box 24)
      - Meeting Minutes (Box 25)
        - 1972/73 (Box 25)
        - 1973 (Box 25)
        - 1974 (Box 25)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
      - New Curriculum Working Papers, 1973 (Box 25)
      - Travel Project, 1972 (Box 25)
      - Workshop, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Topical Files, 1968-1980
    The Dean Davis Topical File (1968-1980) primarily dates from 1972 to 1978. Its arrangement is alphabetical. Areas of particular interest include curriculum and minority affairs.
    - Academic Services, Office of, 1975-1977 (Box 25)
    - Administrative Staff Meetings, 1974 (Box 25)
    - Admissions Standards, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
    - Affirmative Action
      - 1977 (Box 25)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 25)
    - American Association of Colleges of Nursing, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
    - American Association of Deans of College and University Schools of Nursing, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
    - Anesthesiology Program (Box 25)
    - Appeals Procedure (Students), 1977/78 (Box 25)
    - Appeals (Faculty), 1975; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Area Chairpersons (Box 26)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 26)
      - Meetings
        - 1976/77 (Box 26)
        - 1977/78 (Box 26)
        - 1978/79 (Box 26)
    - Audio-Visual, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Black Faculty Caucus, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Budget
      - 1973/74 (Box 26)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 26)
    - Chemistry III, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Clinical Instructor Title Change, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Community Health Nursing, 1973-1978 (Box 26)
    - Connors, Edward J., University Hospital, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Construction Contract, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Continuing Education
      - General, 1972-1978 (Box 26)
      - Application for Accreditation, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Continuing Education Services, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Criterion Measures of Nursing care, 1976 (Box 26)
    - Couzen's Program, 1970-1974 (Box 26)
    - Curriculum (Primarily Syllabi)
      - Fundamentals of Nursing, 1973 (Box 26)
      - Graduate Study, 1974/75 (Box 27)
      - Medical-Surgical (N431, 435, 437)
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
        - 1973/74, 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1974/75 (Box 27)
      - Nursing and Health (N240), 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Nutrition (N226)
        - 1973 (Box 27)
        - 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Parent-Child Nursing
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
        - 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Program, 1973 (Box 27)
      - Process of Disease (N230, 231) and Professional Nursing Matrix (N265), 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Psychiatric Nursing
        - 1972/73 (Box 27)
        - 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Public Health Nursing (N441, 451), 1973/74 (Box 27)
      - Syllabi (Miscellaneous), 1973/74; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Undergraduate Program Philosophy, 1973 (Box 28)
    - Davis, Carolyne K.
      - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 28)
      - Vita (Box 28)
    - Dress Code, University Hospital, 1974 (Box 28)
    - Facilities
      - General, 1969-1973 (Box 28)
      - Report on Needs, March 28, 1973 (Box 28)
      - Assessment of Potential Interim Sites, 1973 (Box 28)
      - Program Statement, 1979 (Box 28)
    - Graff, Louis (Director, Health Science Information Services), 1976 (Box 28)
    - Health Program (Box 28)
    - Health Sciences, Division of